pudhari.co.in 2018-12-31

# 

Pudhari is a popular Marathi daily published from Maharashtra,

Pudhari is a popular Marathi daily published from Maharashtra, Goa and North Karnataka.[1][2] It is the leader in Western Maharashtra and third-largest Marathi newspaper daily in Maharashtra.[3] Pudhari has different editions for major districts of Maharashtra namely Mumbai, Pune, Kolhapur, Sangli, Satara, Nasik, Solapur, Ahmadnagar, Ratnagiri, Sindhudurg, Belgaum, Thane, Raigabd, Aurangabad, Marathawad, Jalana & an edition for Goa state. 

Pudhari endeavors to be a fearless, secular, progressive & objective platform for socio-political discourse, enlightenment and change. It seeks to impart the most relevant information intellectually enrich and empower its readers. 

Thank you for visiting www.pudhari.news 

We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website(s) unless you volunteer to provide that information to us. 

If you visit our website(s) just to browse, read pages or download information, but do not register for any of our services, we gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information cannot and does not identify you personally. 

The kind of information that is gathered automatically include the type of browser, type of Operating System, the date and time of your visit and the pages you visit and the domain name of your Internet Service Provider. 

This non-personally identifiable information is only to improve our website(s) design, content and primarily to give you a better browsing experience. 

We collect personal information from you only if you provide it voluntarily. The type of personally identifiable information that may be collected by us include name, address, e-mail address and information about your interests in and use of various services. 

Our website(s) sometimes contain links to other websites whose privacy policies may be different to ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

We also use a reputable third party to serve the advertisements that you see on our pages. In the course of serving advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique “cookie” on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Our website(s) has links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) are not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information. 

Head Office : 

Pudhari Bhavan   
2318, C Ward, Bhausingji Road   
Phone : 0231-6659999,   
2543111/2/3/4  
Fax : 0231-2543124/5  
Email : news.kop@pudhari.co.in
